Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Records UA045
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Reports, 1970 -- 2006; 1987 -- 2001; UA045.002; 7.0 Linear Feet
  - Reports and Strategic Plans, 1980 -- 1998; UA045.002.004
    - Art & Art History [Strategic Plans], 1983 -- 1993; UA045.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Aidekman Art Gallery [Strategic Plans], 1994 -- 1995; UA045.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Center for Environmental Mgt [Strategic Plans], 1992; UA045.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Center for Public Service [Strategic Plans], 1987; UA045.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Chemistry [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Child Study [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Classics [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Community Health [Strategic Plans], 1992; UA045.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
    - Dean of Students [Mission Statements], 1989; UA045.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - Drama & Dance [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
    - Education [Strategic Plans], 1987; UA045.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - English [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
    - Experimental College [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1993; UA045.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - Geology [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - German, Russian, Asian Languages [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1997; UA045.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - History [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - Library [Strategic Plans], 1991; UA045.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
    - Mathematics [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
    - Museum School [Strategic Plans], 1996; UA045.002.008.00036 (Box 8)
    - Music [Strategic Plans], 1987; UA045.002.008.00037 (Box 8)
    - Occupational Therapy [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1993; UA045.002.008.00038 (Box 8)
    - Philosophy [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00039 (Box 8)
    - Physical Education/Athletics [Strategic Plans], 1987; UA045.002.008.00040 (Box 8)
    - Physics & Astronomy [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00041 (Box 8)
    - Political Science [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00042 (Box 8)
    - Psychology [Strategic Plans], 1987; UA045.002.008.00043 (Box 8)
    - Romance Languages [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1994; UA045.002.008.00044 (Box 8)
    - Sociology & Anthropology [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00045 (Box 8)
    - Urban & Environmental Planning [Strategic Plans], 1987 -- 1992; UA045.002.008.00046 (Box 8)
    - Visual & Critical Studies [Strategic Plans], 1995 -- 1997; UA045.002.008.00047 (Box 8)
    - Wright Center [Strategic Plans], 1994; UA045.002.008.00048 (Box 8)
    - Department Chairs, 1986 -- 1987; UA045.002.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - Engineering School: Annual Reports and Strategic Plans, 1974 -- 2006; UA045.002.005
    Annual reports, general reports, and strategic plans from the school of engineering. Some materials deaccessioned from this file unit, see Collection Documentation for description.
    - Annual Report: CEEO/ The Center for Engineering Education Outreach, 2005 -- 2006; UA045.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Chemical Engineering, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Civil Engineering, 1996 -- 2000; UA045.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Electrical Engineering [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1999; UA045.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Electrical Engineering [2 of 2], 1999 -- 2001; UA045.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Dean of Engineering, 1995 -- 2000; UA045.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Electro-Optics Technology Center, 1991 -- 1996; UA045.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Gordon Institute, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Mechanical Engineering, 1996 -- 2000; UA045.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report: Office of Internships and Corporate Relations, 2001; UA045.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plans: Chemical Engineering, 1988 -- 1993; UA045.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plans: Civil Engineering, 1988 -- 1992; UA045.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plans: Electrical Engineering, 1988 -- 1992; UA045.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plans: Engineering, 1987; UA045.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plan: 1999-2003 College of Engineering, UA045.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plan: Engineering Design, 1987; UA045.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
    - Engineering Psychology, Human Factors Program, 1992; UA045.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
    - Engineering Design, 1974 -- 1992; UA045.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
    - Strategic Plan: Mechanical Engineering, 1989 -- 1994; UA045.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
    - Biotech Initiative, 1993; UA045.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
    - Engineering Accreditation, 1982; UA045.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
    - Engineering Bray/Anderson, 1985 -- 1993; UA045.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
    - Visiting Committee Engineering, 1984; UA045.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
    - EE/CSC Merger, 1987 -- 2001; UA045.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
    - Biomedical Engineering Program, 1989 -- 1993; UA045.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Burns Security Report, 1979; UA045.002.006
    These materials were collected by Russell Miller for his research purposed. DCA reintegrated materials into appropriate collection on 2008-05-06.
    - Burns Security Report, 1979; UA045.002.020.00010 (Box UA045 Shared 1)
  - College of Engineering, annual reports, 1984 -- 1998; UA045.002.007
    These materials were moved from UA007/003 as they fit with this collection more cohesively. VAM and ALG--4/3/09.
    - Annual report, 1984 -- 1985; UA045.002.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1985 -- 1986; UA045.002.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1988; UA045.002.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1989; UA045.002.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1989 -- 1990; UA045.002.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1990 -- 1991; UA045.002.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1992; UA045.002.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1993; UA045.002.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1994; UA045.002.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1994 -- 1995; UA045.002.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Annual report, 1997 -- 1998; UA045.002.021.00011 (Box 21)
- Department Files, 1970 -- 2001; UA045.003; 8.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of correspondence, proposals, and reports regarding departments and centers that reported to the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering. Some annual reports may also be included within these files.
  This series is organized by accession. Arts and Sciences Departments arranged alphabetically by department, followed by Engineering Departments arranged alphabetically by department.
  - American Studies, 1987 -- 1996; UA045.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - American Studies, 1982 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - American Studies, 1979 -- 1981; UA045.003.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Art History, 1986 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Art and Art History, 1990 -- 1998; UA045.003.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Arts Complex, 1987 -- 1995; UA045.003.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Biology [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Biology [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Biology, 1990 -- 2001; UA045.003.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - BSOT, 1983 -- 1986; UA045.003.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - BSOT [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - BSOT [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1987; UA045.003.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - BSOT [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1997; UA045.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - BSOT [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1997; UA045.003.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Center for Children and Media, 1995; UA045.003.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - [Center for Study of] Decision Making, 1980 -- 1992; UA045.003.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Center for Electro-Optics [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1994; UA045.003.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Center for Electro-Optics [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1994; UA045.003.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Center for Interdisc. Studies [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1998; UA045.003.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Center for Interdisc. Studies [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1998; UA045.003.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - [Center] Nuclear Age History and Humanities Center (NAHHC) [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1991; UA045.003.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - [Center] Nuclear Age History and Humanities Center (NAHHC) [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1991; UA045.003.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Center for Reading and Language Research, 1998; UA045.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA045.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA045.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Child Development [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1999; UA045.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Child Development [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1999; UA045.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Classics, 1984 -- 1997; UA045.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Community Health Adv Comm, 1977 -- 1984; UA045.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Community Health [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1997; UA045.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Community Health [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1997; UA045.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Computer Science, 1987 -- 1996; UA045.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Dance, 1970 -- 1982; UA045.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Dance, 1982 -- 1993; UA045.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Drama/Dance [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1993; UA045.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Drama/Dance [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1993; UA045.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Economics, 1985 -- 1999; UA045.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Education, 1998; UA045.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Education, 1985; UA045.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Education, 1994 -- 1998; UA045.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Education Dept, 1994; UA045.003.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Education, 1987 -- 1992; UA045.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Education, 1984 -- 1987; UA045.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Education Department Accreditation, 1987; UA045.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Education Dept. State Visit, 1989; UA045.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Education Evaluation, 1989; UA045.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Education Certification Visit etc, 1993; UA045.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Education Department Accreditation, 1990; UA045.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - English, 1985 -- 1995; UA045.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - English Writing, Lit Materials, 1976 -- 1990; UA045.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Experimental College, 1987 -- 1994; UA045.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Geology, 1975 -- 1996; UA045.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - German/Russian, 1985 -- 1996; UA045.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - History, 1985 -- 1989; UA045.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - History, 1990 -- 1996; UA045.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - International Relations, 1984 -- 1990; UA045.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - International Relations, 1991 -- 1997; UA045.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Mathematics, 1984 -- 1991; UA045.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Music [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1999; UA045.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Music [2 of 2], 1984 -- 1999; UA045.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Peace and Justice Program, 1983 -- 1994; UA045.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Philosophy, 1985 -- 1998; UA045.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Physical Education [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1999; UA045.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Physical Education [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1999; UA045.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Physical Education, 1990 -- 1998; UA045.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Physics, 1971 -- 1979; UA045.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Physics, 1978 -- 1982; UA045.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Physics High Energy [1 of 3], 1982 -- 1991; UA045.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Physics High Energy [2 of 3], 1982 -- 1991; UA045.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Physics High Energy [3 of 3], 1982 -- 1991; UA045.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Physics, 1986 -- 1996; UA045.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Political Science, 1974 -- 1981; UA045.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Political Science, 1981 -- 1983; UA045.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Political Science, 1983 -- 1987; UA045.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Political Science, 1987 -- 1995; UA045.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Psychology, 1970 -- 1982; UA045.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Psychology, 1982 -- 1987; UA045.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Psychology, 1987 -- 1996; UA045.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Religion, 1973 -- 1995; UA045.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Strategic Plans: Religion, 1992 -- 1997; UA045.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Romance Languages, 1975 -- 1983; UA045.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Romance Languages [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1999; UA045.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Romance Languages [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1999; UA045.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Sociology/Anthropology, 1974 -- 1983; UA045.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Sociology/Anthropology [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1995; UA045.003.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Sociology/Anthropology [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1995; UA045.003.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - UEP [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1998; UA045.003.014.00003 (Box 14)
    Urban and Environmental Planning
  - UEP [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1998; UA045.003.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization, 1986 -- 1987; UA045.003.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization, 1987 -- 1988; UA045.003.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization [1 of 3], 1989 -- 1998; UA045.003.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization [2 of 3], 1989 -- 1998; UA045.003.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization [3 of 3], 1989 -- 1998; UA045.003.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - World Civilization Program Proposal, 1990; UA045.003.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - World Civ. Report to NEH 92, 1992; UA045.003.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Biotech Engg Ctr, 1985 -- 1987; UA045.003.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Biotech Eng Ctr, 1987 -- 1992; UA045.003.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Chemical Engg, 1974 -- 2000; UA045.003.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Civil Engineering [1 of 3], 1987 -- 2001; UA045.003.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Civil Engineering [2 of 3], 1987 -- 2001; UA045.003.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Civil Engineering [3 of 3], 1987 -- 2001; UA045.003.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Electrical Engg, 1980 -- 1991; UA045.003.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Engineering, 1987 -- 1988; UA045.003.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Engineering, 1988; UA045.003.015.00001 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Engineering, 1974 -- 1991; UA045.003.015.00002 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Engineering [1 of 3], 1992 -- 1996; UA045.003.015.00003 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Engineering [2 of 3], 1992 -- 1996; UA045.003.015.00004 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Engineering [3 of 3], 1992 -- 1996; UA045.003.015.00005 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Mechanical Engg, 1974 -- 1994; UA045.003.015.00006 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Asian Student Center, 1983 -- 1993; UA045.003.28.00001 (Box 28)
  - Asian Studies, 1983 -- 1998; UA045.003.28.00002 (Box 28)
  - African-American Center, 1970 -- 1999; UA045.003.28.00003 (Box 28)
  - Counseling Center, 1976 -- 1997; UA045.003.28.00004 (Box 28)
  - Center of South Asian and Indian Ocean Studies, 1997 -- 2001; UA045.003.28.00005 (Box 28)
  - Communications & Media Studies, 1981 -- 2000; UA045.003.28.00006 (Box 28)
  - Day Care Center, 1970 -- 1989; UA045.003.28.00007 (Box 28)
  - Environmental Studies, 1991 -- 2000; UA045.003.28.00008 (Box 28)
  - Hispanic American Center, 1993 -- 1996; UA045.003.28.00009 (Box 28)
  - Iberian Democracy Conference, 1995; UA045.003.28.00010 (Box 28)
  - Japan Forum, 1993 -- 1997; UA045.003.28.00011 (Box 28)
  - Japanese Studies, 1981 -- 1994; UA045.003.28.00012 (Box 28)
  - Korean Studies, 1993 -- 1996; UA045.003.28.00013 (Box 28)
  - Latin American Studies, 1982 -- 1995; UA045.003.28.00014 (Box 28)
  - Writing Across the Curriculum [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1998; UA045.003.28.00015 (Box 28)
  - Writing Across the Curriculum [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1998; UA045.003.28.00016 (Box 28)
  - Women's Center, 1975 -- 1988; UA045.003.28.00017 (Box 28)
  - Women's Studies & Women's Programs Board, 1986 -- 1997; UA045.003.28.00018 (Box 28)
  - World Civilisation, 1989 -- 1995; UA045.003.28.00019 (Box 28)
  - Wright Center for Sci and Teaching [1 of 2], 1985 -- 2000; UA045.003.28.00020 (Box 28)
  - Wright Center for Sci and Teaching [2 of 2], 1985 -- 2000; UA045.003.28.00021 (Box 28)
- Building and Construction Proposals and Plans, 1976 -- 2006; 1980 -- 1988; UA045.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials related to various building projects and proposals on multiple Tufts University Campuses.
  This series is arranged alphabetically within each accession.
  - [Campus Center-Program and Site Evaluation-Draft], 1976; UA045.004.015.00007 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Campus Center-Proposal], 1980; UA045.004.015.00008 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Campus Center-Proposal], 1980; UA045.004.015.00009 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Campus Center], 1982; UA045.004.015.00010 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Enhanced Library Service the Liberal Arts, Science and Technology on the Medford Campus-Construction Feasability Study], 1988; UA045.004.015.00011 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate.
  - [Facilities for the Sciences], 1981; UA045.004.015.00012 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Facilities for the Sciences], 1982; UA045.004.015.00013 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Health Sciences Education Building], 1978; UA045.004.015.00014 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Health Sciences Education Building-Preliminary Financial Impact Report], 1982; UA045.004.015.00015 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Pearson Chemistry Building-Master Plan], 1982; UA045.004.015.00016 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - [Planning the Campus], 1982; UA045.004.015.00017 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Chemistry Building, 1999 -- 2002; UA045.004.015.00018 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Chemistry Building-Chemistry Grant Proposal NIH Construction, 1999 -- 2000; UA045.004.015.00019 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Chemistry Building-Keck Foundation Proposal, 2001; UA045.004.015.00020 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Chemistry Building [1 of 2], 2001 -- 2005; UA045.004.015.00021 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Chemistry Building [2 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA045.004.015.00022 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Infrastructure, 1999 -- 2002; UA045.004.015.00023 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Infrastructure-Power Outages Summer, 2002; UA045.004.015.00024 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Psychology Research-NIH Grant Proposal, 1999; UA045.004.015.00025 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Psychology Research, 2006; UA045.004.015.00026 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Psychology Research-NIH Grant Award Notice, 2000; UA045.004.015.00027 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Psychology Research-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1998 -- 2002; UA045.004.015.00028 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Psychology Building Meeting Minutes, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.004.015.00029 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Psychology Building Notice of Federal Interest, 1999 -- 2006; UA045.004.015.00030 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Residence Hall, 2003 -- 2004; UA045.004.015.00031 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
  - Building Projects-Science Technology Center, 1986; UA045.004.015.00032 (Box UA045 Shared 2)
- Subject Files, 1946 -- 2006; 1980 -- 1989; UA045.005; 5.8 Linear Feet
  This series consists of subject files related to special projects and departments, visiting committees and orientations for new departmental chairs.
  This series is arranged alphabetically within accession.
  - Committee Files and Chair Orientations, 1948 -- 2001; UA045.005.001
    Earlier files from an unknown accession are arranged alphabetically, followed by files from accession 2008.019 related to orientation sessions for new departmental chairs.
    - Committee on University Art Collections (CUAC), 1987 -- 1988; UA045.005.016.00001 (Box 16)
    - Computer Institute, 1982 -- 1984; UA045.005.016.00002 (Box 16)
    - Special Studies Enrollment Data, 1948 -- 1975; UA045.005.016.00003 (Box 16)
    - Special Studies Enrollment Data, 1955 -- 1975; UA045.005.016.00004 (Box 16)
    - Library Committee, 1981 -- 1987; UA045.005.016.00005 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committees, 1974 -- 1988; UA045.005.016.00006 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee American Studies, 1989; UA045.005.016.00007 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Arts, 1981; UA045.005.016.00008 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Art History, 1987; UA045.005.016.00009 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Campus Life, 1987; UA045.005.016.00010 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Chemistry, 1986; UA045.005.016.00011 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Chemistry, 1966 -- 1981; UA045.005.016.00012 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Community Health, 1986; UA045.005.016.00013 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Computer Science, 1986; UA045.005.016.00014 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Decision Making, 1989; UA045.005.016.00015 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Economics, 1985; UA045.005.016.00016 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Education, 1986; UA045.005.016.00017 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Peace and Justice, 1989; UA045.005.016.00018 (Box 16)
    - Visiting Committee Soc/Anthro, 1987; UA045.005.016.00019 (Box 16)
    - Chairs' Orientation, 1994; UA045.005.016.00020 (Box 16)
    - Chairs' Orientation, 1995; UA045.005.016.00021 (Box 16)
    - Chairs' Orientation, 1996; UA045.005.016.00022 (Box 16)
    - Chairs' Orientation, 1997; UA045.005.016.00023 (Box 16)
    - 1998 Chairs' Orientation, UA045.005.016.00024 (Box 16)
    - New Chairs Orientation 98-99, 1998 -- 1999; UA045.005.016.00025 (Box 16)
    - Procedures-New Dept. Chairs and Program Directors Orientation, 1999; UA045.005.016.00026 (Box 16)
    - New Chair Orientation, 1998; UA045.005.016.00027 (Box 16)
    - NS/SS [Natural Sciences and Social Sciences] Chairs Meeting 98-99 to 00-01, 1998 -- 2001; UA045.005.016.00028 (Box 16)
    - Susan Ernst Chron Files: Science Chairs Mtgs., 1997 -- 2000; UA045.005.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Russell Miller Subject Files, 1956 -- 1984; UA045.005.002
    - Folder 1 Administration Deans [Russell Miller Subject Files], 1956 -- 1984; UA045.005.020.00009 (Box UA045 Shared 1)
  - War assets administration, 1946 -- 1948; UA045.005.003
    Material added from UA007 as it fit more cohesively with this collection. VAM and ALG--4/3/09.
    - War assets administration [packet] 1 of 18, 1946 -- 1948; UA045.005.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - War assets administration [packet] 2 of 18, 1948; UA045.005.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - War assets administration [packet] 3 of 18, 1948; UA045.005.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - Instructions concerning surplus property [packet] 4 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00004 (Box 22)
    - Surplus property needed received in depts [packet] 5 of 18, 1946 -- 1947; UA045.005.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Surplus property made available [packet] 6 of 18, 1946 -- 1947; UA045.005.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - WAA worksheets [packet] 7 of 18, 1946 -- 1947; UA045.005.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Surplus worksheets [packet] 8 of 18, 1946 -- 1947; UA045.005.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - WAA orders [packet] 9 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00009 (Box 22)
    - WAA purchase orders approved [packet] 10 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00010 (Box 22)
    - Non available mat [packet] 11 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00011 (Box 22)
    - WAA sales documents [packet] 12 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00012 (Box 22)
    - Waiting shipment [packet] 13 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00013 (Box 22)
    - Bills of lading [packet] 14 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00014 (Box 22)
    - Payment of checks [packet] 15 of 18, 1946 -- 1947; UA045.005.022.00015 (Box 22)
    - Check receipts air material command [packet] 16 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00016 (Box 22)
    - Pending [packet] 17 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00017 (Box 22)
    - Ordnance research laboratory and measurement techniques [packet] 18 of 18, 1947; UA045.005.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Historical Subject Files, 1976 -- 2006; UA045.005.004
    - 8 Semester Rule, 1986 -- 1991; UA045.005.025.00001 (Box 25)
    - Accreditation Sub Group File, 1992 -- 2001; UA045.005.025.00002 (Box 25)
    - Animal Per Diem Costs, 2001 -- 2004; UA045.005.025.00003 (Box 25)
    - A&S Department Chairs and Program Directors Meetings, 2005 -- 2006; UA045.005.025.00004 (Box 25)
    - A&S Chairs/Program Directors Meetings, 2004 -- 2005; UA045.005.025.00005 (Box 25)
    - [AS&E Dept. Chair/Program Directors Meetings and Correspondence, 2001 -- 2003; UA045.005.025.00006 (Box 25)